# matthew kohl

San Antonio, Texas, United States



mattkohl82@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/matthewkohl85

# Summary

Experienced Driver with a demonstrated history of working in the restaurants industry. Skilled in jQuery, Bootstrap, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), Management, and HTML. Strong operations professional with a Associate's degree focused in History from St. Philip's College.

Here's a link to my Portfolio https://mattkohl82.github.io/react-portfolio/

### **Experience**



Driver

Domino's

May 2010 - Present (10 years 8 months +)



#### 🧙 Management

Pizza Hut 2004 - 2010 (7 years)

#### **Education**



# The University of Texas at Austin

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development, Web Development 2020 - 2020 24 week full-stack web developer course



### St. Philip's College

Associate's degree, History 2003 - 2015

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



The Coding Boot Camp at UT Austin: Web Development - UT Austin Boot Camps

#### **Skills**

Management • JavaScript • HTML • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • Materialize CSS • CSS Grid Layout • ¡Query